[{"answer": "I have to go meet my friend. Want to come up to her lot, check out her paintings", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Letter.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "There's nothing to get", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": " Yeah, sure", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Letter.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "I am an ar", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "My father gave me four tickets to the that place game for Saturday afternoon. Owner's box, first row behind the dugout", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Letter.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Oh, well. I'm not gonna go without you. Do you guys want 'em", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "I was all primed for the first ro", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Letter.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Oh, there's better,  right there, that's better", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": " You're supposed to do that", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Letter.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "I'd rather go to a hanging", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Well maybe you should ask him", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Letter.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "No! I don't have to take it off, why should I take it off? This is ridiculous!", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "my friend, we are at a baseball game! This is that place", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Letter.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "Well, I don't care, I'm not taking it off", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Hey! Just wait a minute. We just got here", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Letter.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": " I'll go get your hat, my friend", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Oh, yeah, yeah, I'm fine, I'm fine.  Hey, we made the paper. Eh? Look at thi", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Letter.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "A picture", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Wh", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Letter.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "OUR PICTURE'S IN THERE?", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Hi, Mr. my friend", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Letter.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "My, my father", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": " Bo", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Letter.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "You said", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Well, I got a plane to catch", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Letter.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "Going to that place. It's a publisher's convention.  Can I have my sports section", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "Look, I'm really getting tired off all the fighting. Maybe we should just end this before we really start hating each other", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Letter.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "Well, I like to remain friends with people I was friends with", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "Why did you even take it? You broke up with her", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Letter.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "You weren't thinking", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": " This was in front of your door", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Letter.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "Hi, my friend", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "Should I", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Letter.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "ALL RIGHT, all right! I'll call her. my friend's apartment, another day. my friend is helping my friend put on her coat. The TV is on a horse race", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "Yeah", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Letter.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "Okay", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "How's it coming", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Letter.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "Seen any good movies lately", "qsentId": 38}]